manulife presents your savings may just
not be enough
sarah is married with two kids and
enjoys life very much if only her friend
adam didn't always tell her she's not
saving enough why bother she wonders epf
will surely cover her needs and in the
meantime she can use some personal loans
and her credit cards
adam totally disagrees epf may not be
enough and accumulating debt is never a
good idea he knows there are great
advantages to making additional regular
savings plus starting early means even
small amounts can yield impressive
results thanks to the compounding effect
moreover there is peace of mind if one's
income is interrupted sarah disagrees
she likes a bit of luxury now not later
adam explains that she can have both for
starters he prefers a savings plan that
provides investment opportunities and
allows him to continue saving even if he
becomes disabled or critically ill
in addition he discovered an innovative
plan that suits sarah's lifestyle and
possibly increases her savings over time
sarah likes the sound of that she could
send her kids to a better school and
start her own business and once the kids
finish their education and the business
is up and running she can use the
additional savings to enjoy life even
more
sarah understands that starting to save
later means there is less time to get
the same result so she would have to set
aside much larger amounts to enjoy a
comfortable future clearly she knows
what she needs to do now
don't delay
talk to us today